<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Journal]]></title><description><![CDATA[A journal/blog maintained by Mees van Dijk]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:38:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Registers, MMIO, MMUs and a HART]]></title><description><![CDATA[Well first of all, it’s been a while and I very much wasn’t sure whether I would
ever write another entry. But I’ve found something very…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/Registers-MMIO-MMUs-HART/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/Registers-MMIO-MMUs-HART/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 08:42:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Well first of all, it’s been a while and I very much wasn’t sure whether I would
ever write another entry. But I’ve found something very interesting on Reddit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday morning I woke up in the house of one of my friend’s parents. We had
had a party the night before and slept over, since it’s far away from where I
live. As I was scrolling Reddit early in the morning I came across a post
mentioning
&lt;a href=&quot;https://osblog.stephenmarz.com/index.html&quot;&gt;someone’s blog about building an OS in Rust for the RISC-V architecture&lt;/a&gt;.
I’ve been playing with my Arduino a little bit lately and I had also already
come across a project that simplifies Rust development on Arduino. I learned to
program the Arduino in C (not the official Arduino C++ suite) in college two
years ago so I already knew a bit about bare metal programming. RISC-V was no
Arduino however, this was a much more complicated integrated instruction set
(ISA) than the one that my Arduino runs. My Arduino, which is an Uno Rev3 runs
on an Atmega328p processor. That chip contains the flash (for storing the
program), eeprom (a sort of non-volatile RAM) and it’s SRAM (actual RAM) all on
the same chip as it’s processor core. This is what’s known as a
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/System_on_a_chip&quot;&gt;System on a Chip (SoC)&lt;/a&gt; and it
combines some parts of a computer all in one chip. The Arduino actually also has
a whole other SoC, an Atmega16u2, as a co-processor which acts as a converter
between the serial interface and USB, basically it handles all USB things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RISC-V is a lot more complicated than this, while also being a good stepping
stone to keep learning more about hardware. RISC-V uses, like Atmel’s AVR, a
&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reduced_instruction_set_computer&quot;&gt;Reduced Instruction Set Computing&lt;/a&gt;
ISA. Which means that instead of thousands of instructions for the CPU, it has a
couple hundred. RISC-V supports a lot more than AVR though. To me, as a relative
noob (who hasn’t even completed that blog series yet), it seems one of the
important differences between the two is the fact that RISC-V has an
unprivileged mode. That means that the CPU can block or alter some of it’s
behaviour when foreign programs are running. Exactly like how some program I
download on my laptop can’t just go and modify my entire computer and hack me.
Granted you can get hacked, but a program can’t &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; do it. The Arduino
doesn’t have that and that’s why writing an OS on an Arduino isn’t as
spectacular. Because you need to trust all the software you put on it with the
whole machine, you might as well write specialised software that skips having a
kernel and OS at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all I’m learning a lot about the RISC-V architecture and how kernel and
OS development works. I’m planning to practice some of it too. I’ll probably do
it on my Arduino, even though it isn’t really useful (as described above). I’ve
been interested in systems development for some time but the blog post series is
a really good kick start to learn a lot more.&lt;br&gt;
If I do end up writing an OS for the Arduino, I’ll write another entry about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a short explanation of the title, MMIO is memory-mapped IO, the MMU is the
memory management unit, which protects the RAM from unauthorized programs and a
HART is a hardware thread AKA processor core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;More interesting links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been researching a lot of stuff related to these topics. If you’re
interested, click some of the links!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://osblog.stephenmarz.com/index.html&quot;&gt;The blog again&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.Arduino.cc/&quot;&gt;Arduino&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rust-embedded/awesome-embedded-rust&quot;&gt;Awesome Embedded Rust&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://riscv.org/technical/specifications/&quot;&gt;RISC-V technical specification&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hobby coding]]></title><description><![CDATA[Coding when I’m home. Unfortunately, it’s not really something I do anymore. While I’ve been using my
mac more and more at home, instead of…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/hobby-coding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/hobby-coding/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Coding when I’m home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, it’s not really something I do anymore. While I’ve been using my
mac more and more at home, instead of my desktop pc, I don’t actually use it to
write code anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I’ve just been way to busy, I still enjoy coding and I really hope I can
rekindle some of my passion for hobby projects. For a while now I’ve been
daydreaming of building a financial bookkeeping application for personal use.
The motivation here is my almost-daily use of another bookkeeping website:
twinfield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twinfield is close to horrible from a user experience perspective, if you ask
me. However, using it for my board job at Cleopatra has inspired me to want to
keep detailed records of my own spending. I’ve looked around for websites or
apps that could solve my problem but they’re all either a bit too simple or
really old and bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll let you know if I manage to start building my own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cya&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleopatra financially]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m (probably) going to be in the board of my student society next year. I’ll be
in a financial role and I’ve been preparing for a couple…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/cleopatra-financials/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/cleopatra-financials/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’m (probably) going to be in the board of my student society next year. I’ll be
in a financial role and I’ve been preparing for a couple weeks now. The
prospective board needs to present a plan they’ve made for their year. This plan
details what strategies and leadership they will exercise in their year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of this plan are the financial budgets, there are two of them, one for the
membership side of things, which includes quarterly contribution and funding
activities. The other budget details the bar and drink/food sales and purchases.
I’m in charge of the bar side of things and since I’ve been preparing and making
the plan for next year, I’ve also made a big complicated budget for the whole
year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I can’t talk about the specifics of the budget or any financial
information about Cleopatra (the society) because of a non-disclosure agreement
, I can tell you that I’ve begun my path to excel (actually google sheets but
what’s the difference) wizardry. The stuff you can do with these applications is
very complex and they’re essentially entire programming environments in
themselves. Just with the common things people want to do made especially easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past three days have mostly been about making the plan and budget, and I
think I have a presentable first version. In making the budget I’ve both talked
to a lot of people and gotten a lot of people’s opinions. Most of people’s
opinions were based off of calculations on historical data that either I or the
current person occupying my prospective role has made. It feels pretty good to
be able to give people new insights just by showing some data in different, nice
ways. It really helps to formulate new estimates if you can use clear, well
analysed historical data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m pretty happy with my budget plan that I have so far, even though it’s not a
very positive outlook on the next year, I believe it’s a realistic one. Because
corona has big effects on bars and cafe’s.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RSS]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey there, I’m just writing this entry to let you know that I’ve added an RSS feed to the
journal. you can find it at this link. You can use…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/rss-feed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/rss-feed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 10:29:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hey there,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m just writing this entry to let you know that I’ve added an RSS feed to the
journal. you can find it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://journal.mees.io/rss.xml&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use this feed to read my blog posts in your favorite RSS reader, or use
&lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com/&quot;&gt;IFTTT&lt;/a&gt; to get my entries in your mailbox!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do want to use IFTTT then check out
&lt;a href=&quot;https://ifttt.com/applets/112937255d&quot;&gt;this applet&lt;/a&gt; that I made to email me the
new entries.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JWT continued]]></title><description><![CDATA[So recently I made my JWT service. It’s
working and nice but I realised this is not “it”. When I started making the JWT
service I didn’t…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/jwt-continued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/jwt-continued/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 08:45:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;So recently I made my &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-/jwt-service&quot;&gt;JWT service&lt;/a&gt;. It’s
working and nice but I realised this is not “it”. When I started making the JWT
service I didn’t really know what jwt was and how it worked. I had sufficient
understanding of cryptography to know what hashes and signatures were and I also
knew the difference between symmetric encryption and asymmetric encryption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I thought though, is that JWT uses one single authoritative server to check
tokens. This way, every time someone wants to verify a JWT they would need to
make another request to the authoritative server to verify the token. A much
better solution to this problem is signing the token with an asymmetric key.
That way you can distribute your public key to everyone that wants to verify
tokens and sign the tokens themselves with your private key. This way JWTs can
really replace or enhance things like Oauth that use third-party authentication
providers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I realised then, is that my JWT service, which uses the HMAC algorithm to
sign the tokens, isn’t that great to use as a microservice. A good way to
improve it would be to have it use an asymmetric key so that other servers can
verify the tokens without having to make that extra request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the goals that I had in mind though, which were to use it for a single
application, the best way would probably be to keep the jwt parts and the rest
of the server together, which allows it to use HMAC and gain the performance
benefits that come with it.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[stateofthe.cards technical choices]]></title><description><![CDATA[This entry outlines the technical decisions that have been made for building the
card game website that my and my project group came up with…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/state-of-the-cards-tech-choices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/state-of-the-cards-tech-choices/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This entry outlines the technical decisions that have been made for building the
card game website that my and my project group came up with. We will make a
modular card game with a card game editor where users can make up their own rules
for games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My project group consists of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ThowV&quot;&gt;Thomas&lt;/a&gt;,
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LutzenH&quot;&gt;Lutzen&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Prusias&quot;&gt;Mike&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-&quot;&gt;me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Frontend framework - &lt;a href=&quot;https://reactjs.org&quot;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the frontend framework we decided to go with react. This is because react is
only the view layer and it leaves us free to choose whatever libraries we want
to use for the state and data-fetching, the controller and model.&lt;br&gt;
Furthermore, react is very popular and has a lot of community support. There are
tons of available resources to help learn react and React, like angular, has a
big company supporting it together with the open source community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;API server - &lt;a href=&quot;https://nodejs.org&quot;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Node.js is chrome’s V8 javascript engine transplanted into a server scenario.
They basically removed the DOM and added IO API’s in order to facilitate server
development. Node has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npmjs.com&quot;&gt;a huge library of packages&lt;/a&gt; which
can greatly simplify development. Express is the server framework we will use.
Express, while not the newest and coolest framework on the block, is very robust
and well tested. It is one of the most popular npm packages and it’s probably
the most popular web framework for Node.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;File server - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nginx.com/&quot;&gt;NGINX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we are building a PWA (progressive web app), we only need to serve a
static bundle as our app, the app will then fetch all the data it needs from the
API by itself. NGINX is a very stable, battle-tested web server. It supports
advanced configuration but also isn’t hard to work with. NGINX can also serve as
a reverse-proxy for our api, which allows us to route requests to the same
domain to multiple different servers&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JWT service]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey I’m back with a second post today, and an exciting one. I actually made
something that I listed in the last post. I made a
JWT service…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/jwt-service/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/jwt-service/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 18:08:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hey I’m back with a second post today, and an exciting one. I actually made
something that I listed in the last post. I made a
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-/jwt-service&quot;&gt;JWT service&lt;/a&gt;. It’s really simple and
doesn’t control adding users to the list, which means that everyone can add
users which is probably not the best. It’s fairly easy to add some more
authorisation though, which is what I’ll do if I need to use this for an actual
project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve used a couple of libraries to create it and they’ve made it very easy to
build the app. I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://expressjs.com/&quot;&gt;express&lt;/a&gt; as the server framework.
For JWT I used the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/auth0/node-jsonwebtoken#readme&quot;&gt;jsonwebtoken&lt;/a&gt; library, which
is also very simple. To store users I used
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/lukechilds/keyv&quot;&gt;keyv&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a very simple key/value store
that has usernames as keys and hashes as values. I don’t need to store the JWTs
anywhere because they can be verified with just the secret. Keyv has a couple of
adaptors that make it easy to connect it to a persistent database, personally I
use postgres. Lastly I needed bcrypt to hash the stored passwords. With these
three libraries the whole service (without user creation auth) is only a single
file of 81 sloc (single lines of code). It only has four methods: &lt;code&gt;/token
&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;/validate&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;GET&lt;/code&gt; on &lt;code&gt;/user&lt;/code&gt; and
&lt;code&gt;POST&lt;/code&gt; on &lt;code&gt;/user&lt;/code&gt;. For specific information on how it
works and to try it out check
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-/jwt-service&quot;&gt;the Github repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create an issue if you think something should be better, I’ll probably extend it
a little bit more with extra data on users and authorization on creating users
but for now it works.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Users app]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy liberation day to all my fellow dutch people. Today, the fifth of may, is
when we celebrate that we’ve been freed from war. Normally I…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/users-app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/users-app/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 08:12:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Happy liberation day to all my fellow dutch people. Today, the fifth of may, is
when we celebrate that we’ve been freed from war. Normally I’d be going to one
of the (free) festivals that are organised each year, but this year that won’t
be an option. So instead I might watch some streams that are organised as a
replacement or maybe (digitally) hang out with some friends. Maybe I’ll build a
thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I wrote my last post I’ve been thinking of things I can build. One of
the things that I came up with is an app. A simple app that has some users and
some passwords. It doesn’t need those users to do anything special,
just let them login in securely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The catch is that I want to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://jwt.io/&quot;&gt;JWT&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;https://graphql.org/&quot;&gt;GraphQl&lt;/a&gt; in it. I think it’ll be fun and a good exercise
to just build a really simple app that has secure login and a database, just
like you would when building a real, production app. I really want to learn
JWT and GraphQL and I think this could be a good way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll let you know how it went when (if) I’m done making it.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Project ideas]]></title><description><![CDATA[I think that because of getting back into actually coding with this project I
might try and do some more projects sometime, hopefully soon…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/project-ideas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/project-ideas/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I think that because of getting back into actually coding with this project I
might try and do some more projects sometime, hopefully soon. This entry will
be a living list of projects or stuff that I want to use in a project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also been doing some Google analytics and search console things. While I
don’t love Google for tracking me, they make cool software. SEO is something I
haven’t really done anything with before. I’ve looked into it a little bit but
most of it is done by a Gatsby plugin that generates a manifest together with an
existing file from the template that I started with that automatically generates
&lt;code&gt;meta&lt;/code&gt; header tags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, what follows is a list of things I want to do or work with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rust-lang.org/&quot;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jwt.io/&quot;&gt;JWT&lt;/a&gt; UPDATE: see &lt;a href=&quot;/jwt-service/&quot;&gt;the post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://graphql.org/&quot;&gt;GraphQl&lt;/a&gt; (more than just Gatsby)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mollie.com/en/&quot;&gt;Mollie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll let you know if I do anything and I’ll keep updating the list when I
think of more things I want to do.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Day two]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been working some more on the blog today. I set up a better way to publish
posts. I now have a separate git repository that is set up…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/day-two/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/day-two/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working some more on the blog today. I set up a better way to publish
posts. I now have a separate git repository that is set up with
&lt;a href=&quot;https://travis-ci.com&quot;&gt;travis-ci&lt;/a&gt;. Every time I push a new commit to the master
branch there travis-ci does a new build.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically I have a script that travis runs that downloads the main code and uses
it’s build script to create a build that includes the posts. Then with some
(fairly easy) travis configuration I got it to automatically publish to Github
pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve also changed some styles on the website to make things more readable. With
those changes the site now has a perfect score in lighthouse. Try it out
yourself and see some fireworks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason I called the project a journal and not a blog is mainly because I
think journal sounds cooler. As I mentioned in my previous post my main
motivation for the project was that I wanted a nice way to look at my private
journal entries. I used to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://dayoneapp.com/&quot;&gt;Day one&lt;/a&gt; a lot and I
liked having a place for my thoughts. Those thoughts however, were not meant to
be made public ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve really enjoyed creating the site and hope to be working on it some more for
a while. I have some more ideas for improvements and to make it actually
interesting I should probably write some more posts so the site actually has
content. If you’re interested in how I made the site check out
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-/journal&quot;&gt;the repo&lt;/a&gt;. This is not the repo the posts and
travis config are stored in though, thats
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mees-/journal-posts&quot;&gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any suggestions
feel free to submit issues or even pull requests if you want. If you submit a pr
with a post to the post repo I might even accept the post as a guest post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Till next time,&lt;br&gt;
Mees&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[First entry]]></title><description><![CDATA[My first entry!   I build this blog application today, well actually yesterday. I built it with
Gatsby. I knew Gatsby from projects I’ve…]]></description><link>https:/journal.mees.io/first-entry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https:/journal.mees.io/first-entry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;My first entry!  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I build this blog application today, well actually yesterday. I built it with
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/&quot;&gt;Gatsby&lt;/a&gt;. I knew Gatsby from projects I’ve done
before but I have to say it was some work to get up to speed with the whole
thing.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I struggled with getting pages to be built from source plugins and such. The
whole platform is fairly easy to use however when you just follow the tutorial.
Which is also what I ended up doing. I also played around with some templates
before settling with the blog template and stripping it of most boilerplate it
had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I initially wanted to develop this application for my private journal but once I
got it running and looking sort of what I want it to look like I couldn’t not
publish it. And since I want to publish it, it should probably have at least one
post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s my first post. I’ll probably (hopefully) make some more improvements. One
thing I want to do is see if there’s any better way to store posts. Currently I
write the post on my mac and build it into the bundle
(with &lt;code&gt;POST_DIR&lt;/code&gt;) but I want to do this online and have it ci-ed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Signing off for now,&lt;br&gt;
Mees&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>